We aren't going to take any of the pins out yet.
We're not going to take anything out.
We're going to add this on so pinning it right perpendicular to how we're going to sew it right along the edge.
At the corner we're going to turn and we are going to give it just a little fold there so it has room to go around the corner.
And in this first step we're going to go ahead and pin all the way up to this point.
So we're going to trim it just past this point and that's as much as we need for the first step.
We're going to go ahead and finish pinning that in place.
Okay, now that we have the binding all pinned on we're going to go ahead and attach it.
We're just going to start at the edge there and sew right along the edge removing the pins as we come to them.
Okay, once we have the first edge completed we're going to pin the binding on the second edge the exact same way only we're going to wrap it around the edge and pin it so that it goes around the edge on both ends and then we're ready to sew the second side on.